downloadyoutubevideo.org 2018-05-04

# Privacy Policy

We at DownloadYoutubeVideo.ORG guarantee our commitment to respecting and protecting your online privacy. his includes your need and your right to know what we do with the personal information you share with us. It also guides our company's policies regarding the management of this data, including how the information is collected, processed, and for what purposes. 

DownloadYoutubeVideo.ORG gives the commitment that we will use the personal data you provide only in ways that are compatible with the following Privacy Policy. 

**Collection and Storage of Personal Information**

DownloadYoutubeVideo.ORG understands the concerns of users and the information they provide. To use our service, you do not need to provide any personal identifiable information. And we do not capture and keep any personally identifiable information. 

**Cookies**

DownloadYoutubeVideo.ORG may send "cookies" to your computer. Cookies are fragments of data sent through the web server and stored in your hard drive. Cookies can't not read the files stored in your computer, nor can they gather information. The purpose of cookies is just to monitor the traffic on the site, so we know which pages you have visited or customized, making it easier for you to download the information the next time you look at our pages. 

DownloadYoutubeVideo.ORG does not sell the information to advertisers, not does it change your computer settings. You can also reset your browser to refuse cookies or to notify you when a cookie is sent, although doing this may interfere with the quality and speed of your browsing experience since some features won't work as they were meant to.
